<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<photos>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce026.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce26.jpg</filename>
		<title>Deep Prajjwalan</title>
		<description>
			Deep Prajjwalan in the begining of the celebration of Freshers Day by Director of UCE Prof. O. P. Chhangani. Standing by him is Chief Proctor Dr. A. K. Dwivedi.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce027.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce27.jpg</filename>
		<title>A-Block</title>
		<description>
			Sign board outside the A-Block showing the direction and the departments in the block.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce028.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce28.jpg</filename>
		<title>River Chambal</title>
		<description>
			A view of River Chambal flowing along the sides of the college campus. In the center of the image are the 4 chimneys of Kota Thermal Power Station.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce029.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce29.jpg</filename>
		<title>Workshops</title>
		<description>
			Various workshops spread in the large campus area behind the blocks.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce030.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce30.jpg</filename>
		<title>Reading Room</title>
		<description>
			A snapshot of the reading room in the central library where students gather to read various newspapers, magzines, journals and other reference books.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce031.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce31.jpg</filename>
		<title>Registration Desk</title>
		<description>
			One of the registration desks of Anukriti'13. From the left - Garima Jain, Sabaa Paraveen Ansari, Samiksha Bansal.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce032.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce32.jpg</filename>
		<title>Anukriti'10 stage</title>
		<description>
			The stage decorated at the time of Anukriti'10 cultural night.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce033.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce33.jpg</filename>
		<title>Jawahar Sagar Dam</title>
		<description>
			A trip of Computer Engg & Info tech students to Rawatbhata included the visit to Jawahar Sagar Hydel Power Plant. The pic shows the outer area of the Jawahar Sagar Dam.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce034.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce34.jpg</filename>
		<title>Song by Mr. Rajeev Rajora</title>
		<description>
			A song being sung By Mr. Rajeev Rajora on the special request of students on the occasion of Anukriti.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce035.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce35.jpg</filename>
		<title>CCAES-13 Introduction</title>
		<description>
			Cloud Computing and its Application in Engineering and Sciences (CCAES-2013) organised under the coordinatorship of Mr. R. K. Bayal. Photo shows him addressing the students and teachers from all over the country.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce036.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce36.jpg</filename>
		<title>Post Office</title>
		<description>
			Snapshot of the post office situated in the alumini block area inside the college campus.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce037.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce37.jpg</filename>
		<title>Anukriti</title>
		<description>
			Crowd occupying the seats for the Anukriti's cultural night.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce038.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce38.jpg</filename>
		<title>Hostel Day</title>
		<description>
			Celebration of the hostel day by the girls of Girls hostel organised annually. From left are- Moon, Sabaa, Poonam, Garima, Samiksha, Jyoti, Pragya, Anupma, Jeetu, Seema.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce039.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce39.jpg</filename>
		<title>Artilary Committee</title>
		<description>
			A poster designed showing the events in the Artilary committee of Anukriti'11.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce040.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce40.jpg</filename>
		<title>Parantha Making Competition</title>
		<description>
			One of the most popular events of Anukriti'13 - Parantha Making competition. Boys making parantha for the competition.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce041.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce41.jpg</filename>
		<title>Sizzlers committee</title>
		<description>
			Notice board decorated by the sizzlers commiittee depicting the events and competitions in their committee.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce042.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce42.jpg</filename>
		<title>Rana Pratap Sagar</title>
		<description>
			The trip to Rawatbhata by Computer Engg & Info tech students also covered Rana Pratap Sagar.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce043.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce43.jpg</filename>
		<title>Freshers Day</title>
		<description>
			The students booking their seats for the cultural programmes on the eve of the Freshers Day.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce044.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce44.jpg</filename>
		<title>Hostel Day celebration</title>
		<description>
			The girls dancing and celebrating the hostel day in the girls hostel.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce045.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce45.jpg</filename>
		<title>Dispensary</title>
		<description>
			The medical facility is available for the students at the dispensary located at the bakery in the campus area.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce046.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce46.jpg</filename>
		<title>D-Block</title>
		<description>
			The D- Block consits of 4 sections for the 1st year course curriculum. This sign board stands outside the D Block.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce047.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce47.jpg</filename>
		<title>Punjab National Bank</title>
		<description>
			The Punjab National Bank has its branch within the campus area of the college. The bank is located in the administrative block where college fees, exam fees and other types of payments are made.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce048.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce48.jpg</filename>
		<title>Mr. Deepak Bhatia singing song</title>
		<description>
			Snapshot of Webmaster and Prof. Mr. Deepak Bhatia singing a song on the special request of students at the time of Anukriti.
		</description>
	</photo>








	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce050.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce50.jpg</filename>
		<title>CCAES-13</title>
		<description>
			IIT Delhi professor giving presentation and delivering lecture on the cloud computing workshop to the participants who came from all over India.
		</description>
	</photo>

</photos>