<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<photos>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce051.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce51.jpg</filename>
		<title>Extra Curricular Activities - NCC</title>
		<description>
			Other than college, students are also involved in extra curricular activities like NCC and get various opportunities. In the snap, Shashank Shovit (2013 batch) gets the opportunity to fly Zen Microlite aircraft. Other students who got the opportunity from the same batch were Komal Choudhary and Vasant Raj Mutha.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce052.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce52.jpg</filename>
		<title>Bakery</title>
		<description>
			Various shops at bakery including refreshment, tea shops, stationary, cyber cafe. Image showing the cyber cafe and refreshment shop.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce053.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce53.jpg</filename>
		<title>Salad Decoration Competition</title>
		<description>
			Another competition - salad decoration competition organised under the Artilary committee of Anukriti'13.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce054.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce54.jpg</filename>
		<title>Lunch at CCAES'13</title>
		<description>
			The participants having lunch at the cloud computing workshop. Cloud Computing and its Applications in Engineering and Sciences (CCAES-2013) was organised under the coordinatorship of Mr. R. K . Bayal.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce055.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce55.jpg</filename>
		<title>Hostel Day</title>
		<description>
			Celebration of hostel day by girls in the girls hostel.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce056.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce56.jpg</filename>
		<title>Rangoli Competition</title>
		<description>
			Image of a rangoli drawn with the help of pulses on the Rangoli competition.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce057.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce57.jpg</filename>
		<title>Anukriti'11</title>
		<description>
			Director and Prof. O. P. Chhangani And Chief Proctor A. K. Dwivedi having seats in the VIP section of Anukriti cultural night.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce058.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce58.jpg</filename>
		<title>Cloud Computing workshop</title>
		<description>
			Participants from all over India concentrating on the Guest Lecture organised under the Cloud Computing and its Applications in Engineering And Sciences (CCAES - 2013).
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce059.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce59.jpg</filename>
		<title>A-Block </title>
		<description>
			Painting drawn on the wall of A-block showing the departments in this block.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce060.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce60.jpg</filename>
		<title>Boys Hostel</title>
		<description>
			1st Year Boys Hostel located seperate from the senior boys hostel.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce061.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce61.jpg</filename>
		<title>Artilary committee </title>
		<description>
			A decoration of the Artilary committee showing the events under the committee at the time of Anukriti'2013.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce062.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce62.jpg</filename>
		<title>Jawahar Sagar Dam</title>
		<description>
			A trip to Jawahar sagar hydel power plant by CS & IT students. The image shows the dam at the backside.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce063.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce63.jpg</filename>
		<title>Extra curricular activities - NCC</title>
		<description>
			Students also take part in various extra curricular activities outside the college. The picture shows the cadets dressed in NCC air wing uniform.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce064.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce64.jpg</filename>
		<title>Central Library</title>
		<description>
			The central library located in the centre of the college area. The upper portion is the book bank and the lower one is the central library which issues reference books.
		</description>
	</photo>
</photos>