<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<photos>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce001.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce01.jpg</filename>
		<title>Swami Dayanand Statue</title>
		<description>
			This statue is situated at Agora near the central library.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce002.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce02.jpg</filename>
		<title>Sunset from boys hostel</title>
		<description>
			A romantic view of sunset seen from the terrace of 1st year boys hostel.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce003.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce03.jpg</filename>
		<title>Cloud Computing workshop</title>
		<description>
			Students and teachers from all over the country participated in the Cloud Computing and its Applications in Engineering and Sciences (CCAES 2013) workshop organised under Mr. R. K. Bayal.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce004.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce04.jpg</filename>
		<title>Proctor Office</title>
		<description>
			Named as proctor office, the building comprises of proctor office as well as examination cell. Management department is also present in other part of the building.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce005.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce05.jpg</filename>
		<title>Teachers Colony</title>
		<description>
			A board outside the teachers colony indicating the directions of the quarters and the girls hostel.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce006.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce06.jpg</filename>
		<title>Scrutny Hall</title>
		<description>
			This big hall is used for cultural scrutinies of various fests. The hall is also used for examination purposes.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce007.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce07.jpg</filename>
		<title>Agora</title>
		<description>
			A view of the agora showing the central library on the right side and the alumini block on the left. The ground in between is known as Agora.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce008.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce08.jpg</filename>
		<title>Proctor Office</title>
		<description>
			Direction showing the chief proctor office and the examination section.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce009.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce09.jpg</filename>
		<title>Anukriti'10 audience</title>
		<description>
			The audience waiting for the Anukriti 10 to begin. Anukriti is a techno cultural fest organised annually.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce010.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce10.jpg</filename>
		<title>Electrical Department</title>
		<description>
			The Electrical Dept faculty having a photoshoot.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce011.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce11.jpg</filename>
		<title>Ramanujam Hall</title>
		<description>
			Ramanujam Hall is big multipurpose hall in front of the Proctor office. This hall is used for guest lectures, scrutinies and examinations.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce012.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce12.jpg</filename>
		<title>T Point</title>
		<description>
			A view of the main entrance road of the college from T Point.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce013.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce13.jpg</filename>
		<title>Rawatbhata trip</title>
		<description>
			Students of Computer Engg & Info. Tech on a trip to Rawatbhata. Rawatbhata is situated approximately 50 kms away from Kota.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce014.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce14.jpg</filename>
		<title>Gymnasium</title>
		<description>
			Gymnasium is located near the University area. The students can enjoy table tennis, badminton, volleyball in addition to the Gym.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce015.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce15.jpg</filename>
		<title>Anukriti'11. Notice board decorations.</title>
		<description>
			Notice boards are decorated on occasion of Anukriti. A look of one of the notice boards.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce016.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce16.jpg</filename>
		<title>Overhead water tank</title>
		<description>
			Water tank situated in between the bakery and the central library. This water tank is also used is physics laboratory for measuring its height.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce017.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce17.jpg</filename>
		<title>Anukriti 12</title>
		<description>
			Crowd sitting at Agora during techno cultural fest Anukriti 12 organised annually.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce018.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce18.jpg</filename>
		<title>Silver Jublee Stage</title>
		<description>
			A view of the silver jublee stage (visible at the rear side of alumini block) from agora. This stage is used for convocation, republic day and many other events.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce019.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce19.jpg</filename>
		<title>Civil Engg Department</title>
		<description>
			B Block also called as the civil engg department was decorated at Anukriti 13. The 2 pictures shown are the logo of the college compared from 1981 to 2006 when the university was formed.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce020.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce20.jpg</filename>
		<title>Rangoli</title>
		<description>
			One of the rangoli drawn at the time of Rangoli competition in Anukriti 11.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce021.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce21.jpg</filename>
		<title>A-Block parking</title>
		<description>
			A view of the A block parking area from the 1st floor corridor of A block.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce022.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce22.jpg</filename>
		<title>A poster of Anukriti</title>
		<description>
			Poster designed on Anukriti.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce023.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce23.jpg</filename>
		<title>Way to girls hostel</title>
		<description>
			The snap shows the way to the girls hostel which is situated in between the teachers colony and surrounded by the teachers' quarters.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce024.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce24.jpg</filename>
		<title>Saree Saree event of Anukriti'13</title>
		<description>
			One of the most popular event Saree Saree organised on Anukriti'13 by the Artilary committee where competition is among the boys who are dressed in saree. In this photo from left -  Neha Jain, Sarita Meena, Shashank Shovit (dressed in saree), Ankita Vijay, Garima Jain.
		</description>
	</photo>
	<photo>
		<thumbnail>uce025.jpg</thumbnail>
		<filename>uce25.jpg</filename>
		<title>B-C Block corridor</title>
		<description>
			A view of the corridor between B- Block and C-Block.
		</description>
	</photo>
</photos>